Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Office Files, 1979-1994; Series II
  - Constituent Correspondence (Samples), 1978-1994; Subseries 9
    - Letter #52001-52600, 2/87-3/87 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Letter #52601-53000, 3/87-5/87 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Letter #53001-53650, 4/87-6/87 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Letter #53651-54650, 5/87-6/87 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Letter #54651-55850, 5/87-6/87 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Letter #55851-56250, 4/87-5/87 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Letter #56251-56900, 5/87-6/87 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Letter #56901-57300, 6/87 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Letter #57301-57850, 6/87-7/87 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Letter #57851-58100, 7/87 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Letter #58101-58800, 7/87-9/87 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Letter #58801-59200, 8/87-10/87 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Letter #59201-59400, 8/87-10/87 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Letter #59401-59900, 9/87-10/87 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Letter #59901-60500, 9/87-11/87 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Letter #60501-61000, 10/87-11/87 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - Letter #61001-61150, 11/87-12/87 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - Letter #61151-61500, 11/87-1/88 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Letter #61501-62100, 12/87-1/88 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Letter #62101-62850, 1/88-2/88 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Letter #62851-63000, 2/88 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Letter #63001-63100, 2/88 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Letter #63101-63250, 2/88-3/88 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Letter #63251-63550, 2/88-3/88 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Letter #63551-63700, 3/88-4/88 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Letter #63701-63900, 1/88-7/88 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - Letter #63901-64000, 3/88-4/88 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Letter #64001-64250, 4/88 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Letter #64251-64500, 3/88-4/88 (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Letter #64501-64900, 4/88-5/88 (Box-folder 58/13)
    - Letter #64901-65200, 3/88-4/88 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Letter #65201-65450, 4/88-5/88 (Box-folder 58/15)
    - Letter #65451-65550, 5/88 (Box-folder 58/16)
    - Letter #65551-65900, 5/88 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Letter #65901-66100, 5/88-6/88 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Letter #66101-66600, 5/88-6/88 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Letter #66601-66850, 6/88-7/88 (Box-folder 59/4)
    - Letter #66851-67500, 5/88-7/88 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - Letter #67501-67550, 7/88-8/88 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - Letter #67551-67750, 7/88-9/88 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Letter #67751-68200, 8/88-10/88 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - Letter #68201-68500, 9/88-11/88 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - Letter #68501-68800, 11/88-1/89 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Letter #68801-69150, 1/89 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - Letter #69151-69650, 1/89-2/89 (Box-folder 59/12)
    - Letter #69651-70000, 1/89-2/89 (Box-folder 59/13)
    - Letter #70001-70500, 2/89-3/89 (Box-folder 59/14)
    - Letter #70501-70800, 2/89-3/89 (Box-folder 59/15)
    - Letter #70801-71400, 3/89-4/89 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Letter #71401-71850, 2/89-4/89 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Letter #71851-72000, 4/89 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Letter #72001-72250, 2/89-4/89 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Letter #72251-72500, 3/89-4/89 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - Letter #72501-72700, 4/89-5/89 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Letter #72701-73000, 4/89-5/89 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Letter #73001-73500, 5/89-6/89 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Letter #73501-73700, 6/89 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Letter #73701-74100, 6/89 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Letter #74401-74450, 6/89-7/89 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Letter #74451-74600, 7/89 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - Letter #74601-74800, 7/89 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Letter #74801-75850, 7/89-9/89 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - Letter #75851-76350, 8/89-9/89 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Letter #76351-76700, 7/89-9/89 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - Letter #76701-77150, 9/89 (Box-folder 60/17)
    - Letter #77151-77300, 9/89 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Letter #77301-77750, 9/89-10/89 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Letter #77751-78100, 10/89-11/89 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Letter #78101-78450, 11/89-11/89 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Letter #78451-78700, 11/89-12/89 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Letter #78701-78900, 11/89-12/89 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Letter #78901-79250, 12/89-1/90 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Letter #79251-79400, 1/90 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - Letter #79401-79650, 11/89-1/90 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Letter #79651-79750, 11/89-1/90 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Letter #79751-79900, 1/90-2/90 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Letter #79901-80100, 1/90-2/90 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Letter #80101-80300, 1/90-2/90 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Letter #80301-80500, 1/90-3/90 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Letter #80501-80600, 2/90-3/90 (Box-folder 61/15)
    - Letter #80601-80700, 1/90-3/90 (Box-folder 61/16)
    - Letter #80701-80800, 2/90-3/90 (Box-folder 61/17)
    - Letter #80801-81100, 3/90-4/90 (Box-folder 61/18)
    - Letter #81101-81300, 3/90-4/90 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Letter #81301-81600, 3/90-4/90 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Letter #81601-81750, 1/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Letter #81751-81800, 4/90 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Letter #81801-82000, 4/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Letter #82001-82150, 4/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Letter #82151-82250, 4/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Letter #82251-82400, 4/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Letter #82401-82484, 5/90 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Letter #82485-82530, 4/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Letter #82531-82700, 4/90-5/90 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Letter #82701-83000, 6/90 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Letter #83001-83250, 5/90-8/90 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Letter #83251-83600, 5/90-6/90 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Letter #83601-84000, 5/90-7/90 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - Letter #84001-84400, 4/90-7/90 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - Letter #84401-84600, 5/90-8/90 (Box-folder 62/17)
    - Letter #84601-84900, 7/90-8/90 (Box-folder 62/18)
    - Letter #84901-85200, 8/90-9/90 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Letter #85201-85500, 6/90-8/90 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Letter #85501-85700, 8/90-9/90 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Letter #85701-85950, 8/90-9/90 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Letter #85951-86250, 7/90-9/90 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Letter #86251-86300, 9/90-10/90 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Letter #86301-86400, 7/90-10/90 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Letter #86401-86450, 9/90-10/90 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Letter #86451-86500, 10/90 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Letter #86501-86600, 10/90 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Letter #86601-86700, 7/90-10/90 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Letter #86701-86755, 10/90-11/90 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - Letter #86756-86900, 9/90-10/90 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - Letter #86901-87052, 9/90-10/90 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - Letter #87053-87100, 10/90 (Box-folder 63/15)
    - Letter #87101-87350, 10/90-11/90 (Box-folder 63/16)
    - Letter #87351-87400, 11/90 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Letter #87401-87564, 10/90-11/90 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Letter #87572-87600, 11/90 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - Letter #87601-87650, 11/90 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Letter #87601-87650, 11/90 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - Letter #87651-87700, 10/90-11/90 (Box-folder 64/6)
    - Letter #87701-87800, 10/90-11/90 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - Letter #87801-87850, 10/90-11/90 (Box-folder 64/8)
    - Letter #87851-87950, 11/90-12/90 (Box-folder 64/9)
    - Letter #87951-88000, 11/90 (Box-folder 64/10)
    - Letter #88001-88150, 11/90-12/90 (Box-folder 64/11)
    - Letter #88151-88200, 11/90-12/90 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - Letter #88201-88250, 12/90 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - Letter #88251-88350, 12/90 (Box-folder 64/14)
    - Letter #88351-88400, 10/90-1/91 (Box-folder 64/15)
    - Letter #88401-88500, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 64/16)
    - Letter #88501-88600, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 64/17)
    - Letter #88601-88751, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Letter #88752-88850, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Letter #88851-88900, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Letter #88901-88950, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Letter #88951-89000, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Letter #89001-89050, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Letter #89051-89100, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Letter #89101-89200, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Letter #89201-89250, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Letter #89251-89300, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Letter #89301-89350, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Letter #89351-89400, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - Letter #89401-89450, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/13)
    - Letter #89451-89555, 1/91 (Box-folder 65/14)
    - Letter #89556-89600, 11/90-1/91 (Box-folder 65/15)
    - Letter #89601-89650, 11/90-1/91 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Letter #89651-89700, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Letter #89701-89750, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Letter #89751-89800, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Letter #89801-89850, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Letter #89851-89900, 11/90-1/91 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Letter #89901-89950, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Letter #89951-90000, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Letter #90001-90050, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Letter #90051-90100, 1/91 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Letter #90101-90150, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Letter #90151-90259, 12/90-1/91 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Letter #90260-90300, 1/91 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Letter #90301-90350, 1/91-2/91 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Letter #90351-90450, 11/90-1/91 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Letter #90451-90600, 1/91 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Letter #90601-90700, 1/91 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Letter #90701-90850, 1/91-3/91 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Letter #90851-91000, 2/91-3/91 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Letter #91001-91100, 1/91-3/91 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Letter #91101-91200, 3/91 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Letter #91201-91350, 2/91-3/91 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - Letter #91801-91900, 4/91 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - Letter #91901-92000, 4/91 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - Letter #92001-92050, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Letter #92051-92100, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - Letter #92101-92200, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/3)
    - Letter #92201-92263, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/4)
    - Letter #92351-92400, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Letter #92401-92500, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Letter #92501-92550, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Letter #92551-92600, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Letter #92601-92700, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 68/9)
    - Letter #92701-92760, 4/91 (Box-folder 68/10)
    - Letter #92761-92800, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 68/11)
    - Letter #92801-92850, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 68/12)
    - Letter #92851-92900, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/1)
    - Letter #92901-92950, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/2)
    - Letter #92951-93000, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - Letter #93001-93050, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - Letter #93051-93100, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - Letter #93101-93150, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Letter #93151-93200, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - Letter #93201-93250, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - Letter #93251-93300, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - Letter #93301-93350, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - Letter #93351-93400, 4/91 (Box-folder 69/11)
    - Letter #93401-93450, 4/91 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - Letter #93451-93500, 4/91 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Letter #93501-93550, 4/91-6/91 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - Letter #93351-93750, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - Letter #93751-93800, 3/91-5/91 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - Letter #93801-93850, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - Letter #93851-93900, 4/91 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - Letter #93901-93950, 3/91-4/91 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - Letter #93951-94000, 4/91 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - Letter #94001-94100, 5/91 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - Letter #94101-94200, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 70/11)
    - Letter #94201-94300, 3/91-5/91 (Box-folder 70/12)
    - Letter #94301-94450, 4/91-5/91 (Box-folder 70/13)
    - Letter #94451-94500, 6/91 (Box-folder 70/14)
    - Letter #94501-94550, 6/91 (Box-folder 71/1)
    - Letter #94551-94600, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/2)
    - Letter #94601-94650, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Letter #94651-94700, 6/91 (Box-folder 71/4)
    - Letter #94701-94750, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/5)
    - Letter #94751-94800, 6/91 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Letter #94801-94850, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/7)
    - Letter #94851-94900, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/8)
    - Letter #94901-95000, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/9)
    - Letter #95001-95100, 5/91-6/91 (Box-folder 71/10)
    - Letter #95101-95200, 7/91 (Box-folder 71/11)
    - Letter #95201-95450, 6/91 (Box-folder 71/12)
    - Letter #95451-95750, 6/91-7/91 (Box-folder 71/13)
    - Letter #95751-95900, 5/91-7/91 (Box-folder 71/14)
    - Letter #95901-96050, 7/91 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Letter #96051-96150, 4/91-8/91 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - Letter #96151-96200, 4/91-7/91 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - Letter #96201-96230, 7/91 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Letter #96231-96300, 4/91-7/91 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Letter #96301-96400, 4/91-8/91 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Letter #96401-96650, 4/91-8/91 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Letter #96651-96700, 7/91-8/91 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Letter #96651-96700, 7/91-8/91 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Letter #96701-96800, 8/91-9/91 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - Letter #96801-96900, 7/91-8/91 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - Letter #96901-96950, 8/91-9/91 (Box-folder 72/12)
    - Letter #96951-97000, 9/91 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - Letter #97001-97050, 9/91 (Box-folder 72/14)
    - Letter #97051-97100, 9/91 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - Letter #97101-97200, 8/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/2)
    - Letter #97201-97300, 8/91-9/91 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - Letter #97301-97400, 8/91-9/91 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - Letter #97401-97550, 9/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - Letter #97551-97600, 9/91 (Box-folder 73/6)
    - Letter #97601-97650, 9/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/7)
    - Letter #97651-97700, 9/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/8)
    - Letter #97701-97800, 8/91-11/91 (Box-folder 73/9)
    - Letter #97801-97900, 8/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/10)
    - Letter #97901-98000, 10/91 (Box-folder 73/11)
    - Letter #98001-98100, 9/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/12)
    - Letter #98101-98200, 8/91-10/91 (Box-folder 73/13)
    - Letter #98201-98300, 10/91 (Box-folder 74/1)
    - Letter #98301-98500, 9/91-11/91 (Box-folder 74/2)
    - Letter #98501-98700, 9/91-11/91 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - Letter #98701-98900, 10/91-11/91 (Box-folder 74/4)
    - Letter #98901-99100, 11/91-12/91 (Box-folder 74/5)
    - Letter #99101-99300, 11/91-1/92 (Box-folder 74/6)
    - Letter #99301-99400, 1/92 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - Letter #99401-99450, 1/92 (Box-folder 74/8)
    - Letter #99451-99500, 1/92-3/92 (Box-folder 74/9)
    - Letter #99501-99550, 1/92-2/92 (Box-folder 74/10)
    - Letter #99551-99750, 1/92-2/92 (Box-folder 74/11)
    - Letter #99751-99850, 9/91-2/92 (Box-folder 74/12)
    - Letter #99851-99900, 9/91-10/91 (Box-folder 74/13)
    - Letter #99901-100000, 9/91-2/92 (Box-folder 75/1)
    - Letter #100001-100150, 2/92-4/92 (Box-folder 75/2)
    - Letter #100151-100200, 2/92 (Box-folder 75/3)
    - Letter #100201-100250, 2/92 (Box-folder 75/4)
    - Letter #100251-100400, 2/92-3/92 (Box-folder 75/5)
    - Letter #100401-100550, 3/92-5/92 (Box-folder 75/6)
    - Letter #100551-100650, 2/92-5/92 (Box-folder 75/7)
    - Letter #100651-100700, 2/92-3/92 (Box-folder 75/8)
    - Letter #100701-100750, 2/92 (Box-folder 75/9)
    - Letter #100751-100850, 2/92-3/92 (Box-folder 75/10)
    - Letter #100851-101000, 2/92-3/92 (Box-folder 75/11)
    - Letter #101001-101050, 3/92 (Box-folder 75/12)
    - Letter #101051-101100, 3/92 (Box-folder 75/13)
    - Letter #101101-101200, 3/92 (Box-folder 75/14)
    - Letter #101201-101300, 2/92-3/92 (Box-folder 76/1)
    - Letter #101301-101500, 3/92 (Box-folder 76/2)
    - Letter #101501-101700, 2/92-4/92 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - Letter #101701-101765, 4/92 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - Letter #101766-101800, 4/92 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - Letter #101801-101850, 4/92 (Box-folder 76/6)
    - Letter #101851-101900, 4/92 (Box-folder 76/7)
    - Letter #101901-101950, 4/91 (Box-folder 76/8)
    - Letter #101951-102000, 4/91 (Box-folder 76/9)
    - Letter #102101-102250, 3/92-4/92 (Box-folder 76/10)
    - Letter #102251-102400, 4/92 (Box-folder 76/11)
    - Letter #102401-102550, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 76/12)
    - Letter #102551-102600, 4/92 (Box-folder 76/13)
    - Letter #102601-102650, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 76/14)
    - Letter #102651-102800, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 76/15)
    - Letter #102801-102900, 5/92 (Box-folder 77/1)
    - Letter #102901-103050, 3/92-5/92 (Box-folder 77/2)
    - Letter #103051-103150, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 77/3)
    - Letter #103151-103250, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 77/4)
    - Letter #103251-103300, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 77/5)
    - Letter #103301-103350, 5/92 (Box-folder 77/6)
    - Letter #103351-103400, 5/92 (Box-folder 77/7)
    - Letter #103401-103500, 3/92-6/92 (Box-folder 77/8)
    - Letter #103501-103600, 4/92-6/92 (Box-folder 77/9)
    - Letter #103601-103750, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 77/10)
    - Letter #103751-103800, 6/92 (Box-folder 77/11)
    - Letter #103801-103850, 5/92 (Box-folder 77/12)
    - Letter #103851-103900, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 77/13)
    - Letter #103901-103950, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 77/14)
    - Letter #103951-104000, 4/92-5/92 (Box-folder 77/15)
    - Letter #100401-104050, 6/92 (Box-folder 78/1)
    - Letter #104051-104150, 2/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/2)
    - Letter #104151-104200, 6/92 (Box-folder 78/3)
    - Letter #104201-104250, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/4)
    - Letter #104251-104300, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/5)
    - Letter #104301-104350, 3/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/6)
    - Letter #104351-104400, 3/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/7)
    - Letter #104401-104450, 6/92 (Box-folder 78/8)
    - Letter #104451-104500, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/9)
    - Letter #104501-104650, 5/92-6/92 (Box-folder 78/10)
    - Letter #104651-104750, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 78/11)
    - Letter #104751-104850, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 78/12)
    - Letter #104851-104950, 7/92 (Box-folder 78/13)
    - Letter #104951-105050, 7/92 (Box-folder 78/14)
    - Letter #105051-105200, 7/92 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Letter #105201-105250, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 79/2)
    - Letter #105251-105300, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 79/3)
    - Letter #105301-105400, 5/92-7/92 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - Letter #105401-105450, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - Letter #105451-105500, 7/92 (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Letter #105501-105650, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - Letter #105651-105800, 6/92-7/92 (Box-folder 79/8)
    - Letter #105801-105900, 7/92 (Box-folder 79/9)
    - Letter #105901-106000, 7/92-8/92 (Box-folder 79/10)
    - Letter #108001-108100, 1/93 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Letter #108101-108200, 1/93 (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Letter #108201-108300, 1/93-2/93 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - Letter #108301-108400, 2/93 (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Letter #108401-108500, 1/93-2/93 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Letter #108501-108600, 1/93-2/93 (Box-folder 80/6)
    - Letter #108601-108650, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 80/7)
    - Letter #108651-108700, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 80/8)
    - Letter #108701-108750, 2/93 (Box-folder 80/9)
    - Letter #108751-108800, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 80/10)
    - Letter #108801-108850, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 80/11)
    - Letter #108851-108900, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 80/12)
    - Letter #108901-108950, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Letter #108951-109000, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/2)
    - Letter #109051-109100, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/3)
    - Letter #109101-109150, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/4)
    - Letter #109151-109200, 2/93 (Box-folder 81/5)
    - Letter #109201-109300, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/6)
    - Letter #109301-109400, 1/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/7)
    - Letter #109401-109500, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/8)
    - Letter #109501-109600, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 81/9)
    - Letter #109601-109650, 3/93-4/93 (Box-folder 81/10)
    - Letter #109651-109700, 2/93-4/93 (Box-folder 81/11)
    - Letter #109701-109800, 3/93-4/93 (Box-folder 81/12)
    - Letter #109801-109900, 4/93 (Box-folder 81/13)
    - Letter #109901-110000, 3/93-4/93 (Box-folder 81/14)
    - Letter #110001-110100, 2/93-3/93 (Box-folder 82/1)
    - Letter #110101-110200, 1/93-4/93 (Box-folder 82/2)
    - Letter #110201-110250, 3/93-4/93 (Box-folder 82/3)
    - Letter #110251-110300, 3/93-4/93 (Box-folder 82/4)
    - Letter #110301-110400, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/5)
    - Letter #110401-110500, 3/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/6)
    - Letter #110501-110600, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/7)
    - Letter #110601-110650, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/8)
    - Letter #110651-110700, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/9)
    - Letter #110701-110800, 3/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/10)
    - Letter #110801-110900, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/11)
    - Letter #110901-111000, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/12)
    - Letter #111001-111200, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/13)
    - Letter #111201-111300, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 82/14)
    - Letter #111301-111350, 4/93-5/93 (Box-folder 83/1)
    - Letter #111351-111400, 5/93 (Box-folder 83/2)
    - Letter #111401-111450, 3/93-6/93 (Box-folder 83/3)
    - Letter #111451-111500, 3/93-6/93 (Box-folder 83/4)
    - Letter #111501-111600, 3/93-6/93 (Box-folder 83/5)
    - Letter #111601-111700, 5/93-6/93 (Box-folder 83/6)
    - Letter #111701-112000, 3/93-6/93 (Box-folder 83/7)
    - Letter #112001-112350, 5/93-6/93 (Box-folder 83/8)
    - Letter #112351-112500, 4/93-7/93 (Box-folder 83/9)
    - Letter #112501-112900, 5/93-7/93 (Box-folder 83/10)
    - Letter #112901-113100, 4/93-7/93 (Box-folder 83/11)
    - Letter #113101-113150, 7/93 (Box-folder 83/12)
    - Letter #113151-113200, 7/93 (Box-folder 83/13)
    - Letter #113201-113300, 4/93-8/93 (Box-folder 83/14)
    - Letter #113301-113350, 7/93-8/93 (Box-folder 83/15)
    - Letter #113351-113400, 7/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/1)
    - Letter #113401-113450, 6/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - Letter #113451-113500, 5/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/3)
    - Letter #113501-113550, 7/93 (Box-folder 84/4)
    - Letter #113551-113600, 7/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/5)
    - Letter #113601-113650, 6/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/6)
    - Letter #113651-113700, 8/93 (Box-folder 84/7)
    - Letter #113701-113800, 8/93 (Box-folder 84/8)
    - Letter #113801-113850, 7/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/9)
    - Letter #113851-113900, 7/93-8/93 (Box-folder 84/10)
    - Letter #113901-113950, 8/93 (Box-folder 84/11)
    - Letter #113951-114100, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 84/12)
    - Letter #114101-114150, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 84/13)
    - Letter #114151-114200, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/1)
    - Letter #114201-114250, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/2)
    - Letter #114251-114300, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/3)
    - Letter #114301-114350, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/4)
    - Letter #114351-114400, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/5)
    - Letter #114401-114450, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/6)
    - Letter #114451-114500, 8/93 (Box-folder 85/7)
    - Letter #114501-114550, 8/93 (Box-folder 85/8)
    - Letter #114551-114600, 8/93 (Box-folder 85/9)
    - Letter #114601-114650, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/10)
    - Letter #114651-114700, 9/93 (Box-folder 85/11)
    - Letter #114701-114750, 8/93-9/93 (Box-folder 85/12)
    - Letter #114751-114800, 8/93-10/93 (Box-folder 86/1)
    - Letter #114801-114900, 9/93 (Box-folder 86/2)
    - Letter #114901-115000, 8/93 (Box-folder 86/3)
    - Letter #115001-115050, 9/93 (Box-folder 86/4)
    - Letter #115051-115150, 8/93-10/93 (Box-folder 86/5)
    - Letter #115151-115200, 10/93 (Box-folder 86/6)
    - Letter #115201-115250, 9/93-10/93 (Box-folder 86/7)
    - Letter #115251-115300, 10/93 (Box-folder 86/8)
    - Letter #115301-115400, 7/93-10/93 (Box-folder 86/9)
    - Letter #115401-115450, 10/93 (Box-folder 86/10)
    - Letter #115451-115500, 10/93 (Box-folder 86/11)
    - Letter #115501-115550, 9/93-10/93 (Box-folder 86/12)
    - Letter #115551-115700, 9/93-10/93 (Box-folder 86/13)
    - Letter #115701-115800, 10/93-11/93 (Box-folder 86/14)
    - Letter #115801-115870, 10/93-11/93 (Box-folder 87/1)
    - Letter #115871-115900, 11/93 (Box-folder 87/2)
    - Letter #115901-116000, 11/93 (Box-folder 87/3)
    - Letter #116000 1-50, 11/93 (Box-folder 87/4)
    - Letter #116000 1-25, 9/93-11/93 (Box-folder 87/5)
    - Letter #116000 1-50, 11/93 (Box-folder 87/6)
    - Letter #116000 1-56, 11/93 (Box-folder 87/7)
    - Letter #116000 1-50, 11/93 (Box-folder 87/8)
    - Letter #116001-116050, 10/93-11/93 (Box-folder 87/9)